(Bernadette:)Howie, I don't want to play
Lego, Toenail or Pill anymore.
(Bernadette:)So, what do you think we
should do with this room?
(Howard:)Well, I was thinking a
home theater or a gaming room...
(Howard:)you know, like a man cave.
(Bernadette:)Why can't it be a woman cave?
(Howard:)As long as it has a home
theater, a video game system
(Howard:)and you're not allowed in it,
(Howard:)you can call it
whatever you want.
(Bernadette:)I'm being serious.
(Howard:)Well, what do you think
we should do?
(Penny:)I don't know,
(Bernadette:)maybe a home office or...
(Sheldon:)Oh.
(Sheldon:)Look.
(Bernadette:)The teddy bear Stuart won the
night we took him to the fair.
(chuckles):
Oh.
(Howard:)He was so excited.
(Penny:)Yeah.
(Bernadette:)You know, no matter
how hard they tried,
(Bernadette:)they could not guess his age.
(Howard:)I'll give it to him
next time I see him.
(Bernadette:)Have you heard from him
since he left?
(Amy(on Skype):)No.
(Howard:)You'd think he would've called
once he got settled in.
(Bernadette:)Hmm. Maybe he's busy.
(Howard:)Too busy to call?
He wasn't too busy
to binge-watch Hot in Cleveland
with my Hulu password.